

YEVHEN DOVHAN'

WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

A front-end developer with almost one year of experience seeking an opportunity to extend web development skills and knowledge.

I like learning in practice and investing in myself so I have a strong desire to dive into new technologies and improve my current skills.

- have experience working in a team
- familiar with different project methodology (Scrum, Kanban)

CORE COMPETENCIES

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- TypeScript
- REST API
- Adaptive layout (grid / flexbox)
- MySQL
- CSS preprocessor SCSS, SASS
- Git
- OOP, SOLID concepts
- Design patterns
- Vue.js (v3)
- Nuxt.js (v3)
- Vue CLI
- Vuex, Pinia
- Vue Router
- Npm, Yarn
- Markdown

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

12.2021 - 05.2022: <u>Home-UI</u> (Internship)

05.2022 - present: Home-UI (Front-end developer)

Project: Home - is an all-in-one social service that will cover all aspects of your communication with your home and neighbors.

Responsibilities:

- New feature developing
- Creating reusable components
- Support legacy code, code refactoring, packaging entities
- Code review
- · Bug fixing
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams

2019 - 2021: Freelance

Have some finished freelance projects, like an ecommerce web store based on OpenCart CMS, visit-card web pages, landing pages based on WordPress CMS.

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Flexibility
- Fast learner
- Focusedness
- Research solutions
- Friendliness
- · Responsibility

LANGUAGES

- English (B2)
- Ukrainian (Native)

EDUCATION

KHERSON STATE AGRARIAN UNIVERSITY Bachelor's degree Agronomy and Miliaration 2008

Basketball team captain

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- 12.2021 SoftServe Academy (Certificate link)
- 04.2020 Responsive Web Design (FreeCodeCamp online), JavaScript algorithms and data structures (FreeCodeCamp online)

CONTACT INFORMATION

- Phone: +38 097 300 70 71
- Email: y.d.devbox@gmail.com
- GitHub: yevhendevbox
- Ukraine, Kyiv region, Bohuslav